Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
So beautiful. What is that? Where am I? Am I... dead?
Did I die?!
Oops, I'm sorry.
You're awake.
Quit babbling like an idiot.
Stop being dramatic.
Yuna? Noelle? Mimosa? Sir Spectacles? You two?
Well, we were worried about you.
I'm so glad you're back with us, Asta. I thought we were going to lose you!
Okay, that's it! This hug's gone on long enough!
That's not gonna help me heal.
I...
i doubt
t
I...
Don't You purge?
It-cold me a time
If some go on, you want me to like-
There's honey coming home
I want you to check
P gehenации control
cos 3 days of high pressure
Secured polls
Creates the em ill
wanting and
Everyone would say this
We would make a benchmark
I would wish me the fire
In the red music
叫ぶんだ
Get down
We all let you down
Beside
Can you bring me down
Back up
Get far out of the sky
Black Clover
It's a
Don't want me to
You know
I'm a fool
I'm a
Black Clover
You know
I'm a
Let's go
English
What?
I've seriously been asleep for a whole day?
That's right
And you had the nerve to snore the entire time
Loudly
That's the exhaustion that comes from fighting with everything you have
We wanted to help you as well
But by the time we'd arrived
The Eye of the Midnight Sun had run away
The work came awfully late
At least we got to take care of you afterwards
Even if we weren't able to join the battle
Your recovery magic really helped
Thank you
Oh no
It was nothing
Really
Klaus actually did most of the work
He hardly ever left your side
Ahem
Well anyway
Thanks to you
The abducted children all returned home safely
And the one who took them
Nij I believe
He's being questioned back at HQ
Although I doubt he can tell us much about the Eye of the Midnight Sun
Since he appears genuinely remorseful
And has demonstrated no malicious intent
He'll be volunteering here at the church's restitution for his crimes
Good
He felt so bad
I was hoping it would be something like that
In any case you did a fine job yet again
If it were me
I wouldn't have allowed the enemy to escape so easily
Yeah well now I'm gonna catch them
You know
I'm not letting you get the better of me
You'll see
I'm just gonna keep getting stronger and stronger
Then I guess I'll just have to keep getting stronger and stronger and stronger
Then I'll just keep getting stronger and stronger and stronger and stronger
I'll work hard until someday I become the Wizard King
Oh just look at you two
You're obviously really good friends
Yeah
Ridiculous
Now that Asta's awake we should be on our way
Yes sir
Oh right I almost forgot
I meant to tell you Sister Teresa just woke up
What?
Ghosh is in there with her now
Thought I might as well pay you a visit since you're conscious you useless old crone
That's not the proper way to speak to someone on her sickbed
Why don't you try that again you delinquent
Why don't I just finish you off you half dead old hag
Go ahead
You'll be right back in prison the second you do you depraved ex-convict
Hey no fighting big brother
Of course Angel whatever you say
Well I suppose I can bring myself to thank you for taking care of Marie you withered old bat
So you've matured just enough to show gratitude when it's warranted then
Also
I'm
I'm glad you didn't die
Is that right?
Well my beautiful little angel
Are you going to praise your big brother for not fighting?
Excuse me
Huh? It's Austin! Yay!
You slept so long I thought you were dead
I'm never gonna die
Oh yeah we'll see about that
Still got a ways to go
Sister! Your wounds healing up alright?
Do I look like some fragile old lady to you
I'm fine
I bet you're anxious to tell Sister Lily about your latest exploits
She'll be thrilled to hear the story I'm sure
You're right she's gonna be so excited
Don't worry Sister Lily
Soon I'll be the wizard king and then I'll come back for you
Come on Asta
It's time for us to be getting back too
Fine
But I gotta make a stop first
I'm so glad you like it
I figured you'd wake up hungry so I wanted to have plenty of food
But I might have made too much
I hate to say it but this is really really tasty
Kill him
Come on big brother
I've still got room left
Die
This is so good
So maybe men really do prefer women who know how to cook
Asta!
Thank you for the robe
Sure
You kept it all clean like you promised right?
Yep
The robe may be clean but that's a lot more than I can say for you
It looks like you really do need me around after all
So she's the girl he fights beside
Well I'm no match for her
Hey it's okay
Asta
Sorry but I'm taking this much at least
If it weren't for you I might have lost Luca and Marco
Thank you
I uh
Um yeah sure no problem just glad I could help
Did she just
No
You done digesting your lunch there little Rasta?
Yes sir
Good
Cause to celebrate your recovery it's time for the Black Bull's traditional eating contest
This time we're feasting on
Fat potato pies
Right
Can we start eating now? I'm starving
Is this actually a Black Bull's tradition?
It's not
Hey you wanna spar?
I gotta make up for missing out on the big fight
It's only been half a day but it feels like forever Marie
Sorry think I'll have to pass
I'd rather not end up in a food coma
I'm passing too
A competition like this is hardly suitable for royalty
You can't just say no!
This competition is mandatory folks
Yabby sir if you would kindly judge the event
Thank you
Fine cut the chit chat and let's get started
Ready
Eat
Ow
It's so yummy
My mouth is totally dry now
I haven't even taken a bite yet so how come my stomach's full already?
I see what you're doing there Finroll
Stop using spatial magic to send your food into Lux's stomach
I'm busted
Sir I'm not very hungry if there were a pretty woman to feed me
You're out
Oh yeah
Let's go! Flame magic explosive
Hurry hitting
Thought it tastes better well done but that's a bit much
You're out too
I'm nowhere near full let's go
Geez Gordon don't sneak up on people like that
You're gonna make me stroke
Nah that's kind of creepy so out
I won't have an appetite until I see my precious Marie again
You two aren't even eating
Out
If I could just have a sip of water
Those losers over there tapped out ages ago
So who do we have left?
It's an awesome dummy showdown
I'm not done yet I'll win this contest without using magic
Just wait and see
The results
With no magic ute the winner was
Well better luck next time kiddo
Whoa but not using magic is my whole identity
Big surprise
That crest
It's a letter from the royal capital
Did something happen?
Are we going?
Stop yapping for a second will ya?
Yes it's from the capital
Looks like the wizard king's asking for you
The wizard king?
The squad captains are getting together for a meeting tomorrow
Says to drag you along too
Whoa what's he want me there for?
Like I know
You're just gonna have to come to the capital and find out
Sir
I've done as you asked
The captains have been notified about tomorrow's meeting
Excellent thank you
As much as I don't want to believe it
I can no longer deny that there's a traitor in our midst
With ties to the eye of the midnight sun
Tomorrow will be our best opportunity to find out who
But
Do you really think it's going to work?
We'll know soon enough
It all depends on Asta
Thank you for waiting
Welcome Captain Yami Tsukihiro of the Black Bulls
And Asta
Sorry um
What's your name?
Right we've never talked before
I suppose I should have introduced myself
How rude
This here is Mushroom Head
Thank you Captain
I'm Mushroom Head
That was both impolite and uncalled for sir
My real name is Marks
And it's my honor to serve at the Wizard King's side
The Wizard King?
Wow Mushroom Head that's amazing
Well it certainly isn't dull anyway
And your captain was only joking
My name is Marks not Mushroom Head
It's been real fun chatting with you Mushroom Head
Now where's the meeting?
My name is Marks sir
The preparations are going to take a little bit longer
Please wait with the other captains
Now Asta
If you would please come with me
I understand you had a particularly fine showing the other day
It's very rare for the Wizard King to give out ten stars at once
No way!
Ten whole stars?
That's awesome!
Hey where are we anyway?
A secret underground prison
Hardly anyone in the capital knows about it
It's where we keep the VIPs so to speak
VIPs? Like who?
You've heard about the members of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
Captured for their part in the attack on the capital
So you've been keeping them down here?
Yes
They've had memory protecting magic cast on them
So we haven't been able to get any intel on their organization
But the Wizard King has an idea
He believes that your anti-magic sword might be able to break the protect spell
That's why you're here
Throughout the attack they always seem to anticipate our next move
That wouldn't be possible unless they were working with somebody inside the capital
I'm afraid that the only explanation is that there's a traitor among us
And somebody who's fairly high ranked at that
A magic knight captain for instance
What? Seriously?
We don't want to believe it either
That's why we need to make absolutely certain
We're here
Right
Hello?
Hi
Come on in Asta
That was some good work the other day
Thanks a lot Wizard King sir
I'll try to keep it up
I'm sorry
I know you must be tired
But you're the only one who can use that anti-magic sword
So...
Incidentally
I heard you fought some of the Midnight Sun's strongest mages
And about their magic
Was it cool?
Um...
Yeah I guess so
Copy magic
It just copies another mage's spell?
Simply amazing
Oh and beast magic
I've never even heard of that before
And spirit magic?
Flame spirit magic?
How marvelous
I wish I could have been there
Uh...
Sorry?
Sir
Calm yourself
Uh...
Right
Sorry
You've heard our plan Asta
I think it just might work
Do you?
Absolutely!
Whatever you need I'm at your service!
Yay!
What'd they bring this little brat here for?
You'll see
That's the kid who uses anti-magic
They'll have him try to dispel the protect magic cast on our memories
No don't!
Keep that thing away from us you slime!
Hi-ya!
All right Marks it's your turn
Sir
Memory exchange magic
Memoire absolute
What's it doing?
This spell lets us communicate directly with their minds
Allowing us to hear only their truthful memories
Which means
They can't hide
Whoa
Yeah amazing right?
Poking around in people's heads like that
It's so cool
Sure
If you don't mind I'm trying to concentrate
Okay
I'm going to ask you some questions
You are to answer them honestly
Understood?
Yes sir
I heard all about your little rumbling neon village
Poor magic night captains and you let a terrorist ringleader get away?
How embarrassing
They were a little tougher than those nobodies from the diamond and spade kingdoms you and your squad went up against
We were in a real battle
That's awfully big talk coming from a man whose squad has fewer stars than mine
He he he
Only because we don't stoop to doing sneaky stuff on the slide
I don't know about this new katana
Just doesn't shine the same
With the ten year payment plan they had me on
I'm going to be in debt for a while
Anyway you need to calm down skinny bones line face
Garbaltron's actually got a point
It's Gelder
Like I'm interested in the opinion of somebody who doesn't have any stars at all
We got plenty of stars
Black ones
You really want to brag about having negative stars?
Will you too be silent foreigners and low-born fools should hold their tongues
What's that? You want to join our crew sir stuffy pants?
This is absurd
We'll never accomplish anything
Not with all these men blathering on
Why do I have to be next to Yami?
Calm down Charlotte don't panic
Just be yourself
We still need an interim captain for the Crimson Lion Kings
Whoever it is will have big shoes to fill
If Wigolion were here he would have had everything settled five minutes after he walked through the door
Why is everyone so gloomy?
Some youthful charm should lighten the mood
Check it out you guys
I'm Captain Forgolion Vermillion
What exactly do you think you're doing?
You may have become a captain at a young age
But you still need to show some respect
Aww
You're a funny one kid
I've kept you all waiting
I apologize for my tardiness
What were you doing
Von Jens?
Oh
Something needed my attention
You're busy
And who would expect it to be otherwise?
The charismatic captain with the most stars to his name this term must have a lot to do
So tell me what is your secret?
How did the Golden Dawn come to be the mightiest of all the Magic Knight squads and in record time at that?
I hear every member of your squad is developing greater talents than would have been expected of them
Do you perhaps have magic that allows you to see into someone's future?
Regrettably I can claim no such power
The members of the Golden Dawn are simply diligent workers
As a matter of fact
I've wanted to ask you, the mighty tycoon, the secret to amassing a fortune
That's a trade secret, I'm afraid
There's something I've noticed for a while now
You've got one hell of a creepy laugh
And you thought today's meeting would be a good time to tell me?
Also, it's scary how much you look like a boneless ham
Tell me, Von Jens
What were you doing on the day of the Distinguished Service Ceremony?
When a captain has knights who are taking part in the ceremony
That captain should also be in attendance
Perhaps there was something that needed your attention that day too, well
I was playing the gentleman's game of chance
Got cleaned out too, you get it
Nobody asked
Oh, the mood's slipping again
I know
And as for you
If you intend to impersonate me, then be prepared
There will be consequences
I can't do it
Turns out those braided bangs are really tough to pull off
You are seriously killing me, kid
Now stop giving Goldie here such a hard time
Oh, and hey
You don't happen to use light magic, do you?
No, I don't
Oh man, it just keeps getting worse
Hey, check this out
Hi, I'm yummy
Okay, now you keep your darn mouth shut, Chuckles
What?
I bet you were babied a lot growing up
But I'm not gonna do that, got it
Time to start acting like a squad captain
I don't get it, he was laughing a second ago
And you, would you quit sleeping all the damn time?
Okay, what is this?
Okay, you're talking with your snores?
Well, I have no idea what you're saying
Ow
Where the hell is Julius?
He's the one who called this meeting in the first place
Don't tell me you forgot about dragging us all down here today
And went running off somewhere
It could happen
Thank you for waiting patiently, everyone
The preparations are complete
However, the captain's meeting will be taking place elsewhere
Get your ass over here, mushroom head
He is really mad
So this is where they stashed you
You doing okay?
Yes, sir
I'm doing fine
Thank you so much for asking
Does he need to take a dump or something?
Excuse me, sir
What is this about?
Those two
They're from the Midnight Sun
Have you learned something from them?
Oh, yes, all kinds of things
Thanks to Marks and Asta
They've become very talkative
But the juiciest tidbit is probably this
It seems
One of you has been working with the eye of the Midnight Sun
Hmmmm I don't think so much for me
you can go down here
of the night
You can adapt your moderate
Capt showed in the URL's description link.
It is not the mostBo bp fish productje
Thank you, time.
Here we go.
Wh Grease the
I
Yeah
Oh
I'm going to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die
Over through the dream life
Go! Memoir absolute!
Uh...
Alright, I'm going to ask you some questions now
Answer them honestly
Yes, sir
If you had to be either the wizard king or a magic geek
Then which of them would you choose?
Magic geek, for sure
I knew it!
Okay then, next question
What do you think about me?
Well, you can be a henpecking nag some of the time
But you're a hard worker and I'm always grateful for you
Do you mean that?
Of course I do!
You're why I can rush through my wizard king duties and focus on being a magic geek
There's a traitor in this dungeon?
But the magic knights are supposed to be people everyone in the clover kingdom can trust
Whoever you are, I'm going to teach you a lesson
Black Clover, page 39
Three Leafs salute
The loot! I'll never forgive the traitor!
I'll never forgive the traitor!
Eğer
queste
Se
De